var quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Everything in React is a - ",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "Module"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "Component"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "Package"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "Class"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Component"
    },
    {
        question: "What is state in React ?",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "A persistent storage"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "An internal data store(object) of a component"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "A package"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "A class"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "An internal data store(object) of a component"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Babel ?",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "A transpiler"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "An interpreter"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "A Compiler"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "Both Compiler and Transpilar"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Both Compiler and Transpilar"
    },
    {
        question: "What is ReactJS ?",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "Server side framework"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "User interface framework"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "A library for building interactive interfaces"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "A library for building interactive interfaces"
    },
    {
        question: "ReactJS uses ____ to increase performance ",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "Original DOM"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "Virtual DOM"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "Both a & b"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Virtual DOM"
    },
    {
        question: "React is ____ ",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "Component based"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "Module based"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "Both a & b"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "Function based"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Component based"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of following is used to pass data to a component from outside? ",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "PropTypes"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "setState"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "render with arguments"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "props"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "props"
    },
    {
        question: "Everything in React is a - ",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "Module"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "Component"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "Package"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "Class"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Component"
    },
    {
        question: "React.js was created by",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "Jordan Walke"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "Jordan mike"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "Tim Lee"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "Jordan Lee"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "Bruce Lee"
            },
            {
                key: "f",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Jordan Walke"
    },
    {
        question: "What create-react-app command do ?",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "update a react app"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "creates new react app"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "install dependencies"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "create a new class"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "create a new function"
            },
            {
                key: "f",
                content: "create a new object"
            },
            {
                key: "g",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "creates new react app"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the declarative way to render a dynamic list of components based on values in an array ?",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "Using the reduce array method"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "With a for/while loop"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "Using the <Each /> component"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "Using the Array.map() method"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Using the Array.map() method"
    },
    {
        question: "What will happen if you render an input element with disabled = {false} ?",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "It will be rendered as enabled."
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "It will be rendered as disabled."
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "It will not be rendered at all."
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "It will be rendered as enabled."
    },
    {
        question: "How can you get the total number of arguments passed to a function ?",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "Using args.length property"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "Using arguments.length property"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "Both a & b"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "Using arguments.length property"
    },
    {
        question: "Which built-in method combines the text of two strings and returns a new string ?",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "append()"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "substr()"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "indexOf()"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "concat()"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "attach()"
            },
            {
                key: "f",
                content: "map()"
            },
            {
                key: "g",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "concat()"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following function of Array object creates a new array with the results of calling a provided function on every element in this array ?",
        answers: [
            {
                key: "a",
                content: "append()"
            },
            {
                key: "b",
                content: "substr()"
            },
            {
                key: "c",
                content: "indexOf()"
            },
            {
                key: "d",
                content: "concat()"
            },
            {
                key: "e",
                content: "attach()"
            },
            {
                key: "f",
                content: "map()"
            },
            {
                key: "g",
                content: "push()"
            },
            {
                key: "h",
                content: "join()"
            },
            {
                key: "i",
                content: "pop()"
            },
            {
                key: "j",
                content: "None of the above"
            }
        ],
        correctAnswer : "map()"
    }
  ];
  
  export default quizQuestions;